<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SubmissionGames</string>
    <string name="games_name">Games Name</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="genre_games">Genre Game</string>
    <string name="about_me">About Me</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="tv_name">Andrico Halim</string>
    <string name="tv_email">andrico.21421007@student.ubl.ac.id</string>
    <string name="tv_share">Share</string>
    <string name="tv_top10games">Top 10 Upcoming Games</string>


    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Assassins Creed Mirage</item>
        <item>Avatar Frontiers of Pandora</item>
        <item>Alan Wake II</item>
        <item>Cities Skyline 2</item>
        <item>EA FC 24</item>
        <item>Forza Motorsport</item>
        <item>Mortal Kombat 1</item>
        <item>Marvel Spiderman 2</item>
        <item>Starfield</item>
        <item>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>Assassins Creed Mirage is an upcoming action-adventure game developed by Ubisoft Bordeaux and published by Ubisoft. It will be the thirteenth major installment in the Assassins Creed series and the successor to 2020s Assassins Creed Valhalla. \nThe game is set to release for Amazon Luna, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Windows, Xbox One and Xbox Series X/S on October 5, 2023.\nAssassins Creed Mirage is an action-adventure stealth game intended to be reminiscent of older Assassins Creed titles, being more linear and story-focused and reducing the number of role-playing elements present in recent installments of the series. Parkour, close-quarter combat, and stealth are core elements of the gameplay. For assassination missions, Mirage adopts the "Black Box" design previously seen in Assassins Creed Unity and Assassins Creed Syndicate, where players have to explore the environment to find different ways to reach and eliminate their targets. The game is set principally in the city of Baghdad, which is divided into four districts, but also features Alamut, the fortress headquarters of the Hidden Ones. Baghdad is much smaller than the worlds of recent Assassins Creed titles, being closer in size to Unitys and Revelations depictions of Paris and Constantinople, respectively. \nSimilarly to previous Assassin protagonists, the main character, Basim, has a large arsenal of weapons and tools at his disposal, including the signature Assassin Hidden Blade, smoke bombs, throwing knives, and poison darts. Both weapons and tools can be upgraded through a skill tree which allows different effects to be applied to them. Basim also has access to both Eagle Vision and an avian companion named Enkidu (after the character from the Epic of Gilgamesh), an eastern imperial eagle that can be used to scout nearby areas. Unlike previous Assassins Creed games which featured avian companions, enemy archers can detect and shoot at Enkidu. </item>
        <item>Avatar: Frontiers of Pandora is an upcoming open world action-adventure game based on the Avatar film series developed by Massive Entertainment and published by Ubisoft. The game is scheduled to release for Amazon Luna, PlayStation 5, Windows, and Xbox Series X/S on December 7, 2023.\nPlayed in a first-person perspective, players take control of a Navi orphan raised and trained as a soldier by the RDA, before being put into suspended animation and waking up fifteen years later in an abandoned facility. The player must embark on a journey across the Western Frontier, a never-before-seen region of Pandora, discovering their origins and organizing the local Navi tribes to fight back against the RDA as they attempt to exploit the natural resources of the Western Frontier. The game’s story is said to be partially tied to the films, while remaining standalone.\nThe game will also support 2-player cooperative multiplayer.</item>
        <item>Alan Wake II is an upcoming survival horror game developed by Remedy Entertainment and published by Epic Games Publishing. A sequel to Alan Wake, the story follows best-selling thriller novelist Alan Wake, who has been trapped in an alternate dimension for 13 years, as he attempts to escape by writing a horror story involving an FBI agent named Saga Anderson. The game is scheduled to release for PlayStation 5, Windows, and Xbox Series X/S on October 27, 2023. Compared to the first Alan Wake game, which was an action adventure game with horror themes, Alan Wake II is a survival horror game played from a third-person perspective. Players play as Alan Wake or Saga Anderson in two separate single-player stories, which can be played in any order the player chooses; although the opening sequence and ending sequence of the game can only be played as Saga and as Alan, respectively.\nWake and Anderson traverse environments and fight enemies using various firearms and a flashlight, the latter of which can be "focused" to render enemies vulnerable to firearm attacks. Focusing the flashlight drains its battery, and players need to strategically use a limited amount of batteries and ammunition in order to survive. When enemies are close, Alan or Saga can perform a dodge maneuver.\nAlan Wake II incorporates detective elements: when playing as Saga, players can always pause the gameplay to access an enemy-free space dubbed the "Mind Place". Described by Remedy as a "3D menu", the Mind Place is a visual representation of Sagas thoughts. In the Mind Place, players manage a pin board in which they can connect clues to piece together the main mystery, as well as profile characters to gather clues.\nA returning element from Alan Wake is manuscript pages: players find pages of a manuscript that foreshadow upcoming events in the story. Unlike the previous game, Alan Wake II features a dialogue tree system.</item>
        <item>Cities: Skylines II is an upcoming city-building game developed by Colossal Order and published by Paradox Interactive. It is a sequel to Cities: Skylines, and expands upon many of the simulation factors such as simulated city and population sizes, and improved traffic AI and management schemes. Like Cities: Skylines, Cities: Skylines II gives the player a virtual plot of land to create a city within. Players can lay down roads, zoning, utilities, and city services to bring in residents and businesses. The player can set city policies like taxes and edicts to influence how the city grows as well as from which they receive funds to continue to expand out the city. /nInitially the player will be limited to one tile of space to build on but can expand out by purchasing additional tiles from city funds. Whereas the first game was limited to 9 tiles covering 36 km2 of area (81 tiles with user modifications) and the remastered edition to 25 (100 km2), Cities: Skylines II will allow players to build out to 441 tiles representing 159 km2 of area. The game will also not have any limits on the number of citizens that are directly simulated by the game, outside of a players computer or console bounds, in contrast to the first game that was limited to around 65,000 citizens. Each map with the game will be based on a preset climate that will influence weather behavior. Weather and the city populations behavior will work on yearly and diurnal cycles, with each in-game day-night equivalent to one month of simulation time. Winter periods will bring impacts of snow and other cold conditions, while summer weather can bring excessive flooding and tornadoes. Such disasters can be mitigated with additional disaster response facilities and services within the city.</item>
        <item>EA Sports FC 24 is an upcoming football video game, developed by EA Vancouver and EA Romania and published by EA Sports serving as the inaugural installment in the EA Sports FC series following the conclusion of EAs partnership with FIFA, and the 31st overall installment, and is set to launch worldwide on 29 September 2023 for Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Windows, Xbox One, and Xbox Series X/S.The Nintendo Switch version of the game runs on the Frostbite game engine for the first time, providing similar gameplay to the PlayStation 4 and Xbox One versions of the game. Switch entries since FIFA 20 had been widely criticised for being released as Legacy Editions; versions of the game where kits, rosters, and stadiums were updated from the previous release, but added no new gameplay features. EA Sports FC 24 introduces a full Ultimate Team experience and VOLTA Football to the Switch. Despite this, it does not support cross-platform play with either PlayStation 4 or Xbox One.\nHyperMotion V\nEA Sports FC 24 features "HyperMotion V" technology, which uses volumetric data captured by cameras around stadiums from over 180 top-tier matches including the UEFA Champions League, UEFA Womens Champions League, Premier League, and La Liga. The "Advanced 11v11 Match Capture" data is used to teach EA Sports FCs proprietary machine learning algorithms, resulting in over 11,000 in-game animations compared to over 6,000 in FIFA 23.</item>
        <item>Forza Motorsport is an upcoming sim racing video game developed by Turn 10 Studios and published by Xbox Game Studios. It will be the thirteenth main installment in the Forza series and it will be release on Windows and Xbox Series X/S. Although it is the eighth Forza Motorsport title, succeeding Forza Motorsport 7, it will be a reboot for the titular sub-series, dropping the sequential numbering from past entries titles. It will use the new Xbox Series X and Series S consoles to render higher definition graphics than its predecessors. Forza Motorsport is a sim racing video game. At launch, Forza Motorsport is projected to have more than 500 vehicles and 800 upgrades. Approximately 80 vehicles from all eras and racing vehicle kinds are among the vehicles that have been so far announced. While over 100 of these will be new to the series, many of them will be returning from earlier Forza Motorsport games.\nThe game will include elements such as ray tracing in real-time on the track, tire wear, dynamic time of day, damage model changes with better-defined damage, and dirt buildup. There will be other effects, such as "animated track life", "physically based lighting and volumetric fog effects", and "a fully procedural cloud system". The game also includes a single-player career mode and several online multiplayer modes. At launch, Forza Motorsport will have four DLC packs available to players.</item>
        <item>Mortal Kombat 1 is an upcoming fighting game developed by NetherRealm Studios and published by Warner Bros. Games. It will be the twelfth main installment in the Mortal Kombat series, serving as both a sequel to Mortal Kombat 11 (2019) and the series second reboot, following Mortal Kombat (2011). The game is set to be released for Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 5, Windows, and Xbox Series X/S on September 14, 2023. \nMortal Kombat 1 has been confirmed to feature a story mode, online multiplayer with rollback netcode, and offline gameplay. The game will introduce a feature called Kameo Fighters, which will provide assistance to the player during fights. These characters will be separate from the main roster, and chosen before each fight. Additionally, the Air Kombat combo system which was featured in both Mortal Kombat: Armageddon and the action spin-off Shaolin Monks returns, and is being refined for this game.</item>
        <item>Marvels Spider-Man 2 is an upcoming action-adventure game developed by Insomniac Games and published by Sony Interactive Entertainment. Based on the Marvel Comics character Spider-Man, it features a narrative inspired by the long-running comic book mythology while also deriving from various adaptations in other media. It is the third entry in the Marvels Spider-Man series, acting as a sequel to Marvels Spider-Man (2018) and a follow-up to Marvels Spider-Man: Miles Morales (2020), with Peter Parker and Miles Morales struggling to navigate the next steps in their personal lives while combatting an assortment of villains. Among them including a private militia led by mercenary Sergei Kravinoff, the monstrous Lizard, and the extraterrestrial Venom symbiote, which bonds itself to Parker and alters his personality, threatening to destroy his personal relationships.\nGameplay builds on the foundation established by its predecessors, with an emphasis on the multiple playstyles afforded by Peter Parker and Miles Morales as their respective Spider-Men. The game expands on their existing traversal and combat abilities, including new web-based gadgets and suits that can be unlocked through progressing the story, as well as introducing the former Spider-Mans symbiote suit, granting Parker completely unique abilities from his previous playable appearance. As with the prior games, content outside the main story route consists of completing side-missions and obtaining collectibles dispersed throughout the games open world sandbox, with the player able to switch between Parker and Morales to complete dedicated objectives for each of them.</item>
        <item>Starfield is an upcoming action role-playing game developed by Bethesda Game Studios and published by Bethesda Softworks. It was announced during Bethesdas E3 presentation in 2018. The game takes place in a space-themed setting, and is the first new intellectual property developed by Bethesda in 29 years. It is scheduled to release for Windows and Xbox Series X/S on September 6, 2023.\nStarfield is an action role-playing video game. Players can switch between a first-person and third-person perspective any time in the game. Starfield features an open world in the form of an area within the Milky Way galaxy, containing both fictional and non-fictional planetary systems, with players being able to land on more than 1,000 planets and an unspecified number of moons and space stations. The majority of the landscapes within the game were procedurally generated; they were subsequently modified and handcrafted content was developed around them. The game will generate the terrain and the alien flora and fauna of a planet depending on the star of its system and its atmosphere, as well as locations of interest as the player approaches a planet. The largest city in the game, New Atlantis, is the largest fictional city Bethesda has developed. As the player explores the game world, they will encounter various non-playable characters (NPCs), some of whom may join the players crew. Such NPCs may aid the player in combat, carry items, or during confrontations, speak to other NPCs on the players behalf. Some may comment on choices the player makes. The player may station crew members at any of their constructed outposts. Each companion character has their own unique skills and abilities. Some recruitable NPCs are able to be romanced by the player.</item>
        <item>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown is an upcoming racing video game developed by KT Racing and published by Nacon. It will be the twenty-first game in the Test Drive series, the first title in the series since 2012s Ferrari Racing Legends, and the third game in the franchise Unlimited reboot, following 2011s Test Drive Unlimited 2.\nIt was reported in December 2016 that French publisher Bigben Interactive (now called Nacon) acquired the Test Drive intellectual property from Atari, with plans to reboot the franchise. In 2018, Bigben announced the acquisition of French game developer Kylotonn, with Roman Vincent, president of Kylotonn suggesting they were working on the next installment of Test Drive. In April 2020, Nacon filed a trade mark to the Intellectual Property Office for Test Drive Solar Crown, the last two words referring to the Solar Crown in-universe racing competition series featured in 2011s Test Drive Unlimited 2.\nThe game will feature a 1:1 recreation of Hong Kong Island as revealed in a trailer released on 6 July 2021 during Nacon Connect 2021. The game will have "a realistic driving experience", indicating that the game will have a realistic handling model and will be more on simulation side, unlike its predecessor Test Drive Unlimited 2.</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_avatarfop</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_aw</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_cs2</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_eafc</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_fm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mk</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_msm2</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_starfield</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_tdusc</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>